Contact

lpacheco1223@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/luis-pacheco-bsn-rn-ccrn-b3b2733a (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare Nursing BLS

Luis Pacheco, BSN, RN, CCRN

Assistant Nurse Manager at Virtua Health

Cherry Hill, New Jersey

Summary

Experienced Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Patient Advocacy, Wound Care, Medical-Surgical, Medication Administration, and Life Support. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor of Science (B.S.) focused in Nursing from Thomas Edison State University.

Experience

Virtua Health

5 years

Assistant Nurse Manager June 2019 - Present (1 year 2 months)

Marlton, New Jersey

Critical Care RN August 2015 - Present (5 years)

Mt. Holly, NJ

Lourdes Health System
ICU/CCU Nurse
February 2013 - June 2016 (3 years 5 months)
Willingboro

Rutgers/Garden State Correctional Facility Staff Nurse June 2012 - September 2014 (2 years 4 months)

HCR Manorcare RN Supervisor April 2012 - February 2013 (11 months)

SunGard
Command Center Specialist
August 2005 - May 2012 (6 years 10 months)

Education

Thomas Edison State College · (2012 - 2014)

Burlington County College Nursing · (2009 - 2011)